What would you say is the worst
financial decision that you've made throughout your life?
Getting involved in things you
don't want to be involved in.
I had this misfortune of doing a construction loan on
a business that I really didn't want to be in.
I got kind of talked into
it with another friend of mine.
It was supposed to be a
temporary construction loan. Everything was collateralized.
The company ended up, the management was failing.
I had to step in and spend a
couple of years of my life turning it around,
only to have the whole
thing because of a tragic accident.
And somebody unfortunately passed away.
It ended up costing the entire company.
I lost close to $3 million on that.
And what that taught me is don't get involved
in something you don't want to get involved in.
And my gut instinct was telling
me from day one, don't do it.
But I ended up doing it anyway.
Then I powered through and thought.
And by circumstance, I wished I'd just never done it.